♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 10=
Yeah, the death is suspicious.
This woman disobeyed
her father's orders,
escaped from wedding first,
and then even murdered her father.
We must eliminate her.
We've reported it to the authorities.
Maybe we should wait for them.
Everyone,
she killed her father today,
and she could kill us all tomorrow.
The Jiang family is rich.
They must have bribed the officials.
We must kill her
before the officials arrive.
- Kill her!
How dare you
abuse private punishment in Fengcheng!
These officials
ignore public outrage
and bend the law to protect criminals.
Even dismembering this woman
would be too lenient.
Insolent!
She is my wife.
With me here,
even if the sky falls,
no one can lay a finger on her.
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
Let's go.
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
Don't worry.
With me here, no one dares to harm you.
It wasn't me.
I believe you.
How could I possibly kill my father?
He is my father.
It wasn't me.
Don't worry.
I will investigate thoroughly,
and find out the truth.
Governor,
Du Xiaolin of Xiaosheng Society
took over the position of president
of Chamber of Commerce from Mr. Jiang,
and ordered his men
to intercept the grain supply
for Fengcheng and the army
at the train station.
He is demanding you
to hand over the murderer.
Send someone to protect Miss Jiang.
I will lead troops to the train station.
Yes!
(Fengcheng Station)
(Whether going or coming,)
(all are but dreamers.)
Extra!
Shocking parricide case in Fengcheng!
President Jiang of Fengcheng
Chamber of Commerce died at home.
The murderer is his own daughter.
Extra!
One newspaper, please.
Okay. Here you go.
Extra!
(President Jiang of Fengcheng
Chamber of Commerce died at home.)
(The murderer is his own daughter.)
(Fengcheng Station)
How dare a bunch of thugs
stir up trouble here!
You are seeking your own doom.
You bent the law for personal gain.
President Du
is merely upholding justice.
How dare you!
You people from Governor Mansion
are all ruthless executioners.
There are so many civilians
on the train.
Aren't you afraid that stray bullets
will harm the innocent?
Kill him!
(The murderer of President Jiang
is his own daughter.)
Impossible.
Miss Jiang would never kill anyone.
Get him!
Go!
- Yes!
I let you leave.
I didn't expect you to be so useless,
unable to even escape from Fengcheng.
It seems our fate is deeply intertwined.
(Daughter of President Jiang
murdered her father)
Go shut down the newspaper offices
that are spreading rumors.
Yes!
Patricide is a heinous crime,
and punishable by death.
Will Miss Jiang be executed?
With me here, who would dare harm her?
But what about her?
Governor Xu, have you considered
what kind of situation she is in now?
She lost her mother at a young age,
and now her father, who she depended on,
has also passed away.
She is now deemed guilty of patricide.
Rumors are like weapons,
killing one invisibly.
With just a gun, can you keep the mouths
of all the people shut in Fengcheng?
If she has to live with the accusation,
what will she become?
♪A fleeting life♪
♪Suddenly it's dusk♪
Xu You'an,
Miss Jiang's wrongful accusation
is partly my fault.
I must clear her name.
♪The moon as before♪
♪A jug of wine in the night rain♪
♪Softly whispers♪
♪No return♪
♪No regret♪
♪Wast even the best times♪
♪Trapped in dawn and dusk♪
♪Candle by the west window♪
♪Burned out this life♪
♪Ending in nothingness♪
Rong Xiaonan,
do you like Chun'er?
Do you know
what it means to like someone?
Of course, I do.
For her, you risked your life
to come to me regardless of the charge
of assassinating Governor.
If you don't like her, then why?
♪Candle by the west window♪
I regard Miss Jiang just as a friend.
I dare to come to you
because I know you won't kill me.
Otherwise, I'd have died long ago.
♪The world's last gamble♪
♪Sighing at the late hour♪
♪No one comes to meet me♪
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪